Kheel, Theodore W. Arbitration files 6021/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Cervis Brenaime) and Evergreen Bus Service, Inc., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  Jan 4
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Alicia Platia, et al.) and Half Hollow Hills Central School District, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  Feb 13
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Raymond Fleming) and Half Hollow Hills School District, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  Feb 5
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Zoom Christopher) and Harbor Transportation, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  April 17
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Louis Felix) and Hogt transportation, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  June 1
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Ismael Cortijo) and Hogt Transportation, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- ATU local 1181-1061 and Interboro Bus Corp. - Flavio Lombardo, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  May 5
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Interboro Bus Company - Edward Goldstein, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  Nov 11
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Interboro Bus Company, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  July 27
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Joseph Kempski) and Jamaica bus co., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  April 10
- ATU local 1181-1061 (Lawten Thompson) and Fanwood Bus Corp., 1983 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  May 10
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Darlene Andrews et al.) and Jo-Lo Bus Company (Box 3, Folder 60)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Habert Alexis) and Jo-Lo Bus Company, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  March 24
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Vito Giannatasio) and Jo-Lo Bus Company, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- ATU local 1181-1061 (Marie Magloire, et al.) and Jo-Lo Bus company, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  June 9
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Giselle Desir) and Jo-Lo Bus Co., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Alfred Durham) and Jo-Lo Bus co., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Lionel Benjamin) and Jo-Lo Bus Company, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (John Leva) and Jo-Lo Bus Co., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  Feb 2
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Lionel Benjamin) and Jo-Lo Bus Company, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  March 18
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Carol fink) and Jo-Lo Bus Co., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Robert Paulstitch) and Jo-Lo Bus Company, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  March 3
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Marie Francoise Blaire) and Jo-Lo Bus Company, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Rosalie Miller) and Lisa Transportation, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  oct 28
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Richard Shannon) and Lonero Transportation, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  Aug 31
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Jirly Bonbon) and Maggie Transportation, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Charles Robinson, et al.) and Metro, Suburban Bus Authority, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Dan Somerville, et al.) and Metro. Suburban Bus Authority, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  Aug 17
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Kenneth Huschon) and Metro, Suburban bus authority, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Locals 1061 and 1181, ATU and Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  Aug 8
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and New Sigma Car Corporation, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Pioneer Bar Corp., 1973-1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  June 28, 1973 - Jan 18, 1980
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Selvin Gibson) and Pioneer Bus Corp., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Steve Ciani) and Pioneer Bus Corp., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Anthony Benigno) and Premier Bus Corp., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Pioneer Bus Corp., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Pioneer Bus Corp., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  July 9
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (James Howell, et al.) and Premier Bus Corp., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Sept 6
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Pioneer Transportation Corp., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Kenneth Hucher)and Pioneer Transportation, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Oct 12
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Joseph Gondek) and Pioneer Transportation Corp., 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Dec 9
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Pioneer Transportation, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  June 22, 1995 - June 26, 1996
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Florentine Polanco) and Pioneer Transportation, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Nov 17
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Clifford Pitter) and Preferred Busing Corp., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Sylvester Woodland) and Pro-Transit, Inc., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Aug 10
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Benjamin Brown) and Pupil Transportation, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Nov 3
- ATU Local 1181-1061 ( Thomas Castro) and Pupil Transportation 1 of 3, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 ( Thomas Castro) and Pupil Transportation 2 of 3, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 ( Thomas Castro) and Pupil Transportation 3 of 3, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Judith Epstein, et al.) and Schenck Town, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Oct 27 - Dec 19
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Jerry Zucker) and Schenck Corp., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Nov 19
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Schenck Town Inc. / Schenck / Universal Bus Corp., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Schenck Joan, Inc., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Schenck Jean, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Marian Scott et al.) and Schenck Town, Inc., 1981 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Dec 12
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Samuel Fain) and Schenck Town, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Samuel Fain, et al.) and Schenck Town, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Emmanuel Ladouceur) and School Bus Management Co., 1998 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  June 3
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Bernard Robinson) and School Bus Management Co., 1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Gary Smith) and Stagecoach Bus Systems, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Stagecoach Bus Systems, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  May 21
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Stagecoach Bus Systems, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Antoine Riche) and Travelways School Transportation, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Julius Caprioli) and Tufaro Transit Company, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Tufaro Bus Company, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  March 3 - April 13
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Tufaro Transportation, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Nov 30, 1995 - Jan 17, 1996
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Angela Harris, et al.) and United Transit, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  March 2
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Frank Carillo) and Varsity Transit, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  Dec 2
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Julia Smith) and Varsity Transit April 25, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Julia Smith, et al.) and Varsity Transit, Inc., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  Oct 16
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Louis McKinney, et al.) and Varsity Transit, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Marie Mayar) and Varsity Transit, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  March 6
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (David Hamilton) and Varsity Transit, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 Michelle Orasio) and Varsity Transit, Inc., 1998 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  Nov 23
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Charles Mahlmeister) and Wasenbech Transit Corp., 1983 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Williston Bus Company, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  March 26 - April 2
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Multiple Companies, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Local 1181-1061, ATU and Interboro Bus Co. and America Bus co. Holiday Pay, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  Nov 20
- Amal. Transition Local 1181-1061 and Master Coachman and Barone Transp., Inc. Easter Week Payment, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Varsity Transit, Inc. and Pioneer Transp. Corp. (Box 4, Folder 49)
- ATU Locals 1181-1061 and Varsity Transit, Inc. and Pioneer Bus Corp., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Locals 726 and 1056 ATU and NYC Transit Authority, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Locals 726 and 1056, Amal. Transit Union and NYC Transit Authority, George Gromek, et al., 1981 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- AFSCME District Council 37 Harriet Hardin) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  March 5
- AFSCME District Council 37 and NYCTA - Marie Clemente, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- AFSCME District Council 37 and NYCTA - Ruth Paige, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- AFSCME Local 1655 and NYC Transit Authority Thomas Bell, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Local 1655, Transit Authority Clerical employees and NYC Transit Authority, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- AFSCME Local 1655 and NYC Transit Authority Minnie Lampell., 1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- District Council 37 of the American Federation of State County, and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO and Local 1655 of AFSCME and NYC Transit Authority, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  July
- District Council 37, AFSCME and Local 1655, AFSCME and NYC Transit Authority, Phillip Rosenberg, et al., 1966 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  April 14
- District Council 37 of the American Federation of State, County, Municipal Employees AFL-CIO and Local 1655 of the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO and New York City Transit Authority, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- District Council 37, AFSCME and Local 1655, AFSCME and NYC Transit Authority Jo An Novi, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  April 1
- district council 37, AFSCME and Local 1655, AFSCME and NYC Transit Authority Jo Ann Novi, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- district council 37, AFSCME and Local 1655, AFSCME and NYC Transit Authority, Article IX, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- District Council 37, Local 1655, AFSCME and NYC Transit Authority, Article XII, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Dec 28
- District Council 37, Local 1655, AFSCME and NYC Transit Authority, Brenda Porter, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- District council 37, Local 1655, AFSCME and NYC Transit Authority, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- district Council 37, Locals 1655, 1407, 154 and NYC Transit Authority, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  April 22
- district council 37, Locals 1655, 1407, 154, AFSCME and NYC Transit Authority Jack Marin, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Suburban Supervisor Association and NYCTA, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  April 18
- Subway Supervisor's Association and NYC Transit Authority, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  April 28
- Subway-Surface Supervisors Association and New York City Transit Authority, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Oct 1
- SSSA and NYCTA - William Morse, et al., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Subway-Surface supervisors association and New York city Transit Authority, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Oct 1, 1978 - Sept 30, 1980
- SSSA and NYCTA, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- SSSA and NYCTA, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Dec 29
- SSSA and NYCTA - Melvin Odum, et al., 1979 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Feb 8
- SSSA (William Kelly, et al.) and NYCTA, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- SSSA and NYCTA, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- SSSA and NYCTA - Edward De La Tone, et al., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  Jan 16
- SSSA(Aaron De Vinsky, et al.) and NYCTA, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- SSSA (Frank Ognibene, et al.) and NYCTA, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  Oct 3
- SSSA and NYCTA - Cetola, et al., 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  Nov 19, 1980 - April 6, 1981
- SSSA and NYCTA - Reginald Lewis, et al., 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Nov 20, 1980 - Nov 11, 1981
- SSSA (Donald Fels) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- SSSA and NYCTA - Daniel Regan, et al., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  July 16
- SSSA and NYCTA - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  Nov 13, 1981 - Oct 5, 1982
- SSSA (James Johnson) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- SSSA and NYCTA - Richard McDaniel, et al., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  July 21
- TSO and MABSTOA, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  March 4, 1964 - July 1, 1970
- TSO and MABSTOA, 1968-1975 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Oct 1, 1968 - Jan 20, 1975
- TSO and MABSTOA - John McCormick, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  Dec 11
- Transit Supervisors Org. and NYC Transit Authority, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  Sept 4
- TSO and MABSTOA - Patrick Leahy, et al., 1969-1976 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  sept 4, 1969 - Nov 16, 1976
- Transit supervisors Organization (TSO) and MABSTOA, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  Oct 16, 1969 - Oct 30, 1974
- TSO, TSB A, QSO and NYCTA and MABSTOA, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- TSO and MABSTOA, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- TSO and MABSTOA - Martin Murphy, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  April 5
- TSO and MABSTOA Aug 14, 1973 - April 6, 1979, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- TSO and MABSTOA - Julius Marshall, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- TWU-NYCTA Health Benefit Trust, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  July 20
- Transport Workers Union of America and New York City Omnibus Corporation, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Transport Workers Union of America CIO and Pan American World Airways, Inc., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  June 22
- Transport Workers Union of America AFL-CIO and Pan American World Airways, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Aug 28
- Transport Workers Union of America AFL-CIO and Pan American World Airways, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Sept 10
- Transport Workers Union of America AFL-CIO and Pan American World Airways, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Sept 11
- TWU Local 100 (Larmont Young, and Airport Service, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 (John Viviano, et al.) and Airport Transportation Service, Inc., 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Oct 31, 1980 - Oct 12, 1983
- TWU Local 100 (Felipe Fernandez et al.) and Airport transportation Service, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  July 30
- TWU Local 100 (Anthony Salgado) and Airport Transportation Service, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Feb 10
- TWU Local 100 (Ricky Whetstone) and Airport Transportation Service, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Feb 16
- TWU Local 100 (Dave Morris) and Airport Transportation Service, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  April 30
- TWU Local 100 (Jane Morris) and Airport Transportation Service, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  July 23
- TWU Local 100 (Michael Maclin) and Airport Transportation Service, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- TWU Local 100 (Anthony Carl) and Airport Transportation Service, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Dec 21
- TWU Local 100 (John Fisher) and Airport Transportation Service, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Jan 26
- TWU Local 100 and Ave. B and E. Broadway Transit - Willie Williams et al., 1959-1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  June 5, 1959 - March 6, 1974
- TWU Local 100 and Ave. B and E. Broadway Transit - Percy Kamminsky, et al., 1959-1966 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Nov 13, 1959 - Nov 30, 1966
- TWU Local 100 and Ave. B and East Broadway Transit, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  July 8
- TWU Local 100 (Edward McGuire) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  July 19
- TWU Local 100 (Thomas Wright, et al.) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- TWU Local 100 (Oliver Tong et al.) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  Sept 9
- TWU Local 100 (Nathaniel Lesesene) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  July 14
- TWU Local 100 (William Ford) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- TWU Local 100 and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- TWU Local 100 (Herbert Lakin et al.) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- TWU Local 100 (Hugh Cox) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  April 29
- TWU Local 100 (Eugene Graddy) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- TWU Local 100 (Vincent Spinelli, et al.) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  Oct 2
- TWU Local 100 (John Grady) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Feb 23
- TWU Local 100 (Michael Smith) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  Jan 11
- TWU Local 100 (Operator Cucciniello et al.) and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  Nov 7
- TWU Local 100 and Ave B and E. Broadway Transit, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- TWU Local 100and Club Transportation Corp., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  Aug 7
- TWU Local 100 (Michael Dimitro) and Club Transportation, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- TWU Local 100 and Club transportation, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  March 29
- TWU Local 100 and Club Transportation Corp. - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1963-1979 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  Oct 1, 1963 - Jan 25, 1979
- TWU Local 100 and Club Transportation Corp., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- TWU Local 100 (Peter Calabrese, et al.) and Club Transportation corp., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  May 7
- TWU Local 100 (Charles Benjamin, et al.) and Club Transportation Corp., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- TWU Local 100 (Earl Monroe et al.) and Club Transportation Corp., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  Oct 27
- TWU Local 100 (Michael Klobnock) and Club Transportation Corp., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- TWU Local 100 (William Fortier, et al.) and Club Transportation Corp., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- TWU Local 100 (John Belfont) and Club Transportation Corp., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- TWU Local 100 and Club Transportation Corp., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  Aug 14
- TWU Local 100 (Michael Calbi) and Club Transportation Corp., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- TWU Local 100 (Dominick Alvarez) and Club Transportation Corp., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- TWU local 100 and Club Transportation corp., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- TWU Local 100 (Benjamin Stutzin) and Club Transportation Corp., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  June 18
- TWU Local 100 (John Davidson) and club Transportation, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- TWU Local 100 and Club Transportation Corp., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  March 10
- TWU Local 100 (Eugene Cerbine) and Club Transportation Corp., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  July 12
- TWU Local 100 (Edward Jones) and Club Transportation Corp., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- TWU local 100 (John Anderson) and Club Transportation Corp., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  Dec 8
- TWU Local 100 and Club Transportation Corp., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  Jan 23
- TWU Local 100 and 5th Ave. Coach Lines, 1959-1964 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  June 25, 1959 - Oct 20, 1964
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica Buses - Miscellaneous, 1945-1980 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  May 1, 1945 - Sept 22, 1980
- TWU Local 100 (Edwin Albers et al.) and Jamaica Buses, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica buses, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica Buses, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  Dec 22
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica Buses, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  April 2
- TWU Local 100 (Edmund Quadrocchi, et al.) and Jamaica Buses, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica buses, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  Jan 12, 1955 - March 15, 1956
- TWU Local 100 (John Muson, et al.) and Jamaica Buses, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  Oct 17
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica buses, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  Jan 24
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica Bus Lines, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  March 21
- TWU Local 100 (Andrew Powel) and Jamaica Buses, 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  April 15, 1957- Jan 20, 1959
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica Buses (Box 6, Folder 68)
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica Buses, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- TWU Local 100 (Melvin Lewis, et al.) and Jamaica Buses, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  Oct 19
- TWU Local 100 (George Tanhouser) and Jamaica Buses, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  May 9
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica Buses - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica Buses, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica Buses, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  Feb 25
- TWU Local 100 (Charles Rosendahl, et al.) and Jamaica Buses, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  March 7
- TWU Local 100 (Thomas Zaccheo, et al.) and Jamaica buses, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  June 25
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica Buses, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- TWU Local 100 (John Pepper) and Jamaica Buses, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  Aug 30
- TWU local 100 (William Alvarez) and Jamaica Buses, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 79)
- TWU Local 100 (Vernon Crawford, et al.) and Jamaica buses, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 80)
- TWU Local 100 (James Leonard) and Jamaica Buses, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 81)
- TWU Local 100 (Vincent Pastore) and Jamaica Buses, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Garvey) and Jamaica Buses, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  July 11
- TWU Local 100 (Teddy Alston, et al.) and Jamaica Buses, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 84)
- TWU Local 100 (Alfred Porter) and Jamaica Buses, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 85)
- TWU Local 100 (Willie McMiller) and Jamaica Buses, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  Oct 14
- TWU Local 100 (Francois Telemaque) and Jamaica Buses, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  Feb 18
- TWU Local 100 and Jamaica Buses, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 88)
- TWU Local 100 (Andrew Masone) and Jamaica Buses, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 89)
- TWU Local 100 (John Pentenero) and Liberty Coaches, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Coaches, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- TWU Local 100 (John Reed) and Liberty Coaches, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Aug 4
- TWU Local 100 (Leif Boro) and Liberty coaches, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Jan 29 - June 11
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Coaches - Frank Clarke, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty coaches, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- TWU Local 100 (Edward Wilson) and Liberty Coaches, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 (James Wallace), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- TWU Local 100 (Herbert Clare, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- TWU Local 100 (Ronald Johnson, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Upshaw) and Liberty Coaches, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 100 (David Allen) and Liberty Coaches Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Nov 14, 1975 - Feb 2, 1977
- TWU Local 100 (Antonio Garcia) and Liberty Coaches, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- TWU Local 100 (Rocco Gerard, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty coaches, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 100 (Daniel Trivero, et al.) and liberty coaches, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- TWU Local 100 (Augie Santos, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  Oct 25
- TWU Local 100 (Miguel Gamez, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- TWU Local 100 (Henry Clare) and Liberty coaches, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  June 30, 1977 - July 20, 1978
- TWU Local 100 (John Rose, et al.) and Liberty coaches, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- TWU Local 100 (Robert Orefice, et al.) and Liberty coaches, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- TWU Local 100 (Ernest Moore) and Liberty Coaches, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- TWU Local 100 (Edward Roberts, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  June 16
- TWU Local 100 (Nathan Jacobs) and Liberty coaches, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Aug 25 - Sept 8
- TWU Local 100 (Ira Goode) and Liberty Coaches, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- TWU Local 100 (James Griffin, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- TWU Local 100 (Charles Price) and Liberty Coaches, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- TWU Local 100 (Daniel DuBose) and Liberty coaches, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- TWU local 100 (Michael Zurich) and Liberty Coaches, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  July 10
- TWU Local 100 (Owen O'Malley, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  Sept 12
- TWU Local 100 (Barry Harris) and Liberty Coaches, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  Dec 10
- TWU Local 100 (Jesse Inclan, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- TWU Local 100 (Carmella Sayegh, et al.) and Liberty coaches, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  Jan 19
- TWU Local 100 (Jeremiah Williams, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Murray, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  March 27
- TWU Local 100 (Eddie Taylor, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  April 7
- TWU Local 100 (Clifford Mitchell) and Liberty Coaches, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  May 22
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Coaches, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Coaches, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  June 24
- TWU Local 100 (J.D.R. Billups, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- TWU Local 100 (Kenneth Kovalich, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  Aug 13
- TWU Local 100 (Susan Terrett et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  Oct 9 - 12
- TWU Local 100 (Muhammed Sharif) and Liberty Coaches, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- TWU Local 100 (Roland Anderson) and Liberty Coaches, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 44)